And I'm going to put a plug
in for Dave in first rehab.
I think that we also have a
lot of young athletes,
and I think we have a lot of
growth in terms of
families.
We all have kids.
And the athletes are just
incredible.
But the problem is, in
Florida, we
have the indulgence of being
able to play all year
round.
And Dave is an expert and
sort of a scientist
of trying to get people back
to their game.
And I always send him these
difficult athletes
and he's gotten back people
back to, you know, MLB
level,
you know, these athletes
back to playing
and being recruited by
national, international
superstars.
But I think the thing is is
that we really have to
realize
that rehab science in these
sports is just as critical,
probably maybe more critical
than even or as much of our
surgical treatments.
You know, Tommy John
surgery, rotator cuff
talk about tennis players,
you talk about pickleball
players,
I mean, baseball players.
And I think that I've sent
you a lot of tough athletes.
I think you really enjoy
those challenges.
I do, I do.
You find the science of it.
And not every therapist does
that, you know?